Guide to the Cornell University Judicial Administrator records, 1871-2014.
Cornell University Judicial Administrator records, 1871-2014.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Judicial Administrator records, 1871-2014.
34-10-1666
Cornell University. Office of the Judicial Administrator.
5 cubic ft.
Files, meeting minutes, correspondence, newspaper clippings, records.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes minutes of Judiciary Board meetings; correspondence; newspaper clippings; material concerning student protest, 1970; records of the Student Conduct Committee, 1931-1968; Student Code, 1871-1959; and other records of the Men's Judiciary Board, the Undergraduate Judiciary Board, and the Freshman Judiciary Board at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes of Judiciary Board meetings; correspondence; newspaper clippings; material concerning student protest, 1970; records of the Student Conduct Committee, 1931-1968; Student Code, 1871-1959; and other records of the Men's Judiciary Board, the Undergraduate Judiciary Board, and the Freshman Judiciary Board at Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Students.
Subjects:
College discipline.; College students--Conduct of life.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access restricted to permission of office of origin. Annual reports in Box 5 are not restricted. Individual case files restricted to permission of student or 80 years after the creation of the record.
CONTAINER LIST
- MJB Minutes; 1953-1954, 1955-1956, 1956-1957, 1957-1958, 1959-1960, Nov. 1956-May 1957, May 1957-Dec. 1958, Jan. 1959-Sept. 1964 (Box 1)
- Review of Disciplinary Action (Box 1)
- MJB (Men's Judiciary Board), Sept. 1960-June 1961, Nov. 1961-Dec. 1961, Jan. 1962-Mar. 1962, Apr. 1962-June 1962 (Box 1)
- FRJB (Freshman Judiciary Board) Minutes, Jan. 1958-Sept. 1964 (Box 1)
- UJB (Undergraduate Judiciary Board) Cases Meetings, 1963-1968 (Box 1)
- MJB Correspondence (Box 1)
- Judiciary Board - Men's (Box 1)
- Referrals to Mental, Referrals to WRJB (Box 1)
- Social Codes (Box 1)
- Publicity - Judiciary Boards, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
- MJB News Clippings (Box 1)
- MJB, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
- FRJB Historical (Box 1)
- FRJB Cases - open file (Box 1)
- MJB Historical (Box 1)
- Men's Judiciary Board, 1963-1964 (Box 1)
- Student Protest and the Law II.: The 1970 Scene (Box 1)
- Student Conduct Committee, 1931-1967 (Box 2)
- SCC; June 1965-June 1967, Oct. 1962-June 1965, Sept. 1957-Sept. 1962, Sept. 1955-June 1967, Aug. 1950-June 1955, Mar. 1931-June 1950 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Records, mostly Faculty Committee on Student Conduct (Box 3)
  Faculty Committee on Student Conduct; 1957-1959, 1959-1962, 1962-1964, 1964-1966, 1966-1968
  Chairman's Folder
  Student-Faculty Boards - Policy and Membership
  Student-Faculty Boards, 1971-1972
  Action Notice, 1965-1971
  Correspondence; 1960-1961, 1961-1962, 1962-1963
  Student Code, 1871-1959
- University Hearing Board and University Review Board, 1969-1974 (Box 3?)
- History of Disciplinary Action (Box 4)
- Student Code - other schools (Box 4)
- Frosh Men's Res. Judicial Board (Box 4)
- Committee on Student Conduct; Sept. 1955-Feb. 1956, Mar. 1956-June 1956, 1956-1957 (Box 4)
- Student Conduct - Regulations (Box 4)
- University Faculty Committee Correspondence (Box 4)
- Codes and Judicial Committee, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Codes and Judicial Committee (1), 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Codes and Judicial Committee (2), 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Codes and Judicial Committee, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Codes and Judicial Committee, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Codes and Judicial Committee, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Codes and Judicial Committee, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Codes and Judicial Committee, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Codes and Judicial Subcommittee, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Advisory Committee on Sanctions, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- University Assembly, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- University Assembly, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Campus Code of Conduct - Drafts, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Changing the Code - Comments, 2006-2008 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Krause Report, April 2006 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Krause Report Responses, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Policy Notebook for the Cornell Community, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Code Changes, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Codes Changes, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Judicial Administrator Search Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Judicial Board Interviews, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Judicial System Orientation, 1992-2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Report on a Review and Proposed Revision of the cornell University Campus code of Conduct, April 3, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Barbara L. Krause
- Bi-Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Codes Counselor, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2008-2009 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2009-2011 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Administrator, 2011-2013 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Annual Report of the Office of the Judicial Codes Counselor, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 38)